Because there are mutual fund people in the market, there is
aggressive demand in the market.
We have some special products which no
one else in the entire industry has. There are
such features due to which the
products of ICICI Lombard are
unmatched in the market. For example, a
product has been launched recently, so people will be wondering
whether such health insurance also exists.
It has such four in-depth features
which no one else in the entire industry has.
You can tell someone that sir, take a policy of
10 lakhs, 20 lakhs, 1 crore, 50 lakhs
or go to ICC Lombard and
say that you can take the same policy of unlimited
[music].
Hello, how are you all friends? Today
we are going to do a very special and wonderful work.
Today Ajay Kumar ji is sitting with me
from ICC Lombard and
he is very welcome to our studio today. There are
many such doubts that people
want to connect with ICC Lombard,
want to know about ICC Lombard,
what are the good things in ICC Lombard,
what kind of process is there, how can we give you
a  You can generate next level income
and there is no job here.
Today we are going to discuss a lot about what is agency business and
Ajay ji, who has been associated with ICC Lombard for a long
time, is going to share all his
inputs with you.
Friends, it is very important to watch this video till the end
and please subscribe to my channel,
share it, comment on it and
definitely click the bell icon, only then
you will keep getting all the latest updates.
Where whoever joins with this mindset
that we have to add part time, let me
tell you that I have seen many such
people who initially start part time
in this business gradually, in
some job, some business, some student
formation or housewife formation and as
they start getting interest, money starts
coming in more, earnings increase, then they
dedicate full time to this business
because the earning in this business is
next level. Here you
get commission from 15 to 40 percent. Our
business has commission slabs based on volume. There is a
separate commission for fresh business in health insurance.  The port business will be separate
and you will get the money for whatever work you do throughout the month
on time, between the 8th and 10th of the next month,
and it will
come directly into your account. There is
no cash system. You don't get any monthly salary from anyone.
Here, there is a part-time business
opportunity and that too by selling commission. You will be
scared. Many myths will come to your mind that you do
n't know
how difficult health insurance is, how will you do it?
I have never sold health insurance,
so you don't have to worry.
We are here for that, our team is here and this is
our expertise. To groom you, to
train you, to teach you the basics and to
upgrade you from the basic to the next level and make you
earn at a different level, this is our
main work. If I talk about ICC Lord's training, there is
regular
training as per the company. I also do
regular training for my teams and you are
in office hours. Sometimes you will face the problem of
how to train in the office,
so you can do our night training.
My training is from 8:00 to 9:00 in the night and from 10 to 11 in the night, which is weekly.
You will get at least two trainings in which
your life can be transformed and let me
also tell you that those who join ICC Lombard through
us will not have to pay
any money for any training or anything for their lifetime,
everything will be absolutely free
and this is a lifelong code,
your code will never be closed, you just have to keep working,
this code is not for those who pass time, if you think that I will just
try it by trial, then the company does
not give the code to the people who are on trial, it is very
strict, the code is
available for those who will work, for those who will not work, there is no code
for them, we have come up with some new initiatives
which are very simple because there are
people from mutual funds in the market, there is
aggressive demand in the market, we have some such
special products which no one else has in the entire industry, there are such
features due to which the
products of ICC Lombard are
unmatched in the market, like
recently a product has been launched, what is its
name, Health Elevate, Health Elevate, this is such a
product, it works like this, when people
have this product  If they represent and
take you there, then people will be left wondering
whether such health insurance even exists, of
four infighting
crores or 50 lakhs, or they
go on behalf of ICICI Lombard and say that you can take sum insurance,
unlimited means there will be no
amount, whatever claim comes, the
company will provide it to you and it will be written in the policy that
your insurance is unlimited,
everything comes unlimited in unlimited, there is no
scope left of any kind, whether
your claim is of 5 crores, 50 crores,
500 crores, the company will provide
this power to you, only ICC
Lombard company provides you which you will
not see
or hear in any other company, till now you must have
heard
that sum insurance is one time, two times, three times, four times, seven times,
times, no, here we will give you unlimited sum
insurance, that means take a policy of 10 lakhs, it will keep
increasing 100 times for life, 10 times, 20 times, 20 times,
30  20 20 of 30 30 of 40
40 of 50 this will keep increasing for life long
wow you can see such features all over India
you will not get it anywhere else and the
premium is very economical you can
try it once, we have a calculator
app called iPartner in which
you can easily calculate the premium which will give you
visibility to everything smoothly it will be
only for you in that
premium suppose if it is an individual then it is
coming to 8 to 000 000 for an individual what do you
want sir it is very cheap
in the entire industry
only a company like Lord can take the first initiative by taking such premium and such features
which no other company is even close to it there is
one more feature
if someone's ex member has taken a policy of 10 lakhs
in his entire life no matter how much claim he gets,
1 crore 2 crore 3 crore 4 crore 5 crore
100 crore the company will settle it completely
one time one claim in life no matter of
any amount  It is a very big thing, if you have taken a
policy of Rs 10 lakh or Rs 20 lakh
and a claim of Rs 1 crore comes, then
it is possible for you, the customer, that company is
giving you the choice of which maximum
claim you can make, you can settle one claim in your life from here,
for which
you do not have to pay any extra money, your entire claim will be
cashless, this is also a unique feature, this is
also available only with Lord,
that is why you should take Lord's agency
and this opportunity can come to you, this is a
100% cashless policy all over pan India,
plus you can try any company's policy,
not this, all the companies are the best,
but ICC Lord has a claim producer option,
you will not have to pay a single rupee
and within 16 seconds our approval comes, in
today's date, Artificial
Intelligence is attached with us, this is the
power, today the company is
working on Artificial Intelligence, if a customer's claim
comes, within 16 seconds our approval
goes.  Yes, it is live sir, I will settle two or three claims also
if you ask, then all this is our
power, when you tell this to your customers
that our
claim center does it, due to which the claims
here are tension free, that is why
people take health insurance, whoever wants to
take tension, he takes some other policy, if he wants to
remain tension free, then he
takes Lombard policy, it is a unique feature
or
[Music]